there are two ways to lead your life
once being Carefree another one is being
careful as we grow and transition into
various stages of Our Lives
we carefully plan and provide for our
future needs
actually we set aside some of the most
cherished desires and passions to be
pursued in the golden Innings of Our
Lives
the beginning of the most awaited phase
but it may also bring with itself a host
of health concerns too but now you can
bid goodbye to concerns and live with
confidence
we have created a healthcare solution
for your golden innings
presenting rcicia Lombard golden shield
with this holistic Healthcare offering
your health concerns won't be a
hindrance in living life to the fullest
after you turn 56.
with lifetime renewals reset benefit and
a Care Management program
Golden Shield fulfills all Health needs
of seniors stay worry-free with
extensive coverage of hospitalization
expenses of the insured person after the
annual sum insured the daycare
procedures or treatments are also
covered
the pre-existing disease waiting period
is comparatively planned and ensures
seamless coverage domiciliary treatment
is also covered under this policy get
coverage for medical expenses on Home
Care treatment up to five percent of
annual salmon short medical expenses
incurred in respect of inpatient ayush
are also covered
medical expenses incurred for an organ
donor's hospitalization for harvesting
of organ donated up to rupees 10 lakh we
also provide coverage for domestic Road
ambulance services to one percent of
annual summon sure and maximum of rupees
10 000 air ambulance expenses are also
covered walk to the annual sum limit get
coverage for modern Medical Treatments
during the policy period as well
get a host of benefits that make this
policy the most attractive senior care
plan against the competition such as
reset benefit enhanced annual sum
insured for road traffic accidents
vaccination incentive annual Health
checkup
an attractive policy to your options you
also get a host of optional covers that
boost the protection and enhance your
peace of mind
what's more this policy comes with a
unique offering the Care Management
program which aims at providing
Solutions focused on promoting overall
well-being of our customers